Contact

davejackson21@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/david-jackson-40b8906b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
ACLS, BCLS
BLS
Nursing

David Jackson

Clinical Implementation Specialist RN, BSN, CMSRN Allentown, Pennsylvania Area

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Telemetry, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), IV Therapy, and Acute Care. Strong healthcare services professional with a BSN from Grand Canyon University.

Experience

The Clinician Exchange
Clinical Implementation Specialist
March 2018 - Present (2 years 4 months)
Various locations

AMN Healthcare Travel RN July 2015 - Present (5 years)

St. David's Medical Center Registered Nurse December 2011 - Present (8 years 7 months) IMC

Float Pool

Austin Community College Medications Assistant January 2013 - May 2013 (5 months)

Assisted the nursing instructor in the clinical setting.

South Jersey Healthcare Registered Nurse July 2010 - November 2011 (1 year 5 months)

Education

Grand Canyon University
BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2010 - 2012)

Helene Fuld School of Nursing
Associate of Science (A.S.), Allied Health · (2007 - 2010)